<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Collapsing_toolbar</string>
    <string name="placeholder">Kotlin is a modern programming language designed to be concise, safe, and interoperable with Java and other languages. It provides many ways to reuse code between multiple platforms, making it a productive choice for developers. Here are some key features and concepts of Kotlin:
        1. Conciseness: Kotlin aims to reduce boilerplate code and increase developer productivity. It has a more compact syntax compared to Java, which allows you to write code in a more concise and expressive manner
        2. Null Safety: Kotlin has built-in null safety features to prevent null pointer exceptions. It distinguishes nullable and non-nullable types, forcing you to handle null values explicitly, which leads to more robust and reliable code.
        3. Interoperability: Kotlin is fully interoperable with Java, which means you can seamlessly use existing Java libraries and frameworks in Kotlin projects. You can call Java code from Kotlin and vice versa without any issues
        4. Extension Functions: Kotlin allows you to extend existing classes with new functions, even without modifying their source code. This feature, called extension functions, enables you to add new functionality to classes from external libraries or even standard library classes.
        5. Data Classes: Kotlin provides a concise way to define classes that are used mainly for holding data. These data classes automatically generate standard methods like equals(), hashCode(), and toString(), making it easier to work with data objects.
        6. Coroutines: Kotlin has built-in support for coroutines, which are lightweight threads that can be used for asynchronous programming. Coroutines simplify asynchronous code by providing a sequential and structured approach to handling asynchronous tasks.
        7. Kotlin Multiplatform: Kotlin offers multiplatform support, allowing you to share code between different platforms, such as Android, iOS, and web. With Kotlin Multiplatform, you can write common business logic once and use it across multiple platforms, reducing code duplication and improving code maintainability.
        These are just a few highlights of Kotlin\'s features and capabilities. To learn more about Kotlin and get started with it, you can refer to the official Kotlin documentation kotlinlang.org. Additionally, there are various online tutorials, courses, and resources available to help you learn Kotlin effectively.</string>
</resources>